我非常喜歡你的作品  湯姆
I just love your writing, Tom,
從《天蝎》開始
ever since Scorpio.
我覺得你寫得越來越好了
I think it just gets better and better.
是嗎  你還讀過哪本
Oh, yeah? What else have you read?
都讀過
All of them.
我覺得你的新書很精彩  《上帝之釜》
I thought the latest was brilliant, God's Cauldron.
-你讀過了  -一口氣讀完的
- You read that? - In one sitting.
但是我們最想讀的一本
But what we'd really love to read
是你那本關于安德伍德夫婦的書
is your book on the Underwoods.
那個改了  改成小說了
Well, it's changed. It's fiction now.
但原型是他們
But based on them.
人們可能會去對比
People might draw parallels.
安德伍德夫婦會喜歡嗎
Would the Underwoods find it flattering?
我覺得他們不會特別喜歡
I don't think they'd be too happy with it.
你覺得會暢銷嗎
How do you think it'll do?
-誰知道  -希望比《上帝之釜》要好
- Who knows? - Better than God's Cauldron, I hope.
銷量不高  是嗎
Sales were disappointing, weren't they?
事實上  你過去十年
In fact, they've been disappointing
寫的每一本書銷量都不高
on everything you've written the past ten years.
我們可以用這本新書來扭轉局面
We can change that with this new book.
我可不是政治工具
I'm not a political tool.
我們接你來  不是因為我妻子是你的粉絲
We didn't fly you up here because my wife's a fan.
你肯定知道我們想要什么
I'm sure you had a notion of what we're after.
我什么想法都沒有
I didn't have any expectations.
我來是出于好奇
I just came because I was curious.
那么讓我來滿足你的好奇心
Well, then let me satisfy your curiosity.
如果你的書能傷到安德伍德夫婦
If your book can hurt the Underwoods,
我們要讓它在競選之前出版
we want it to be published before the election,
并且要讓它暢銷
and we want it to be big.
戴娜·崔斯特  你認識吧
Dana Treister, do you know her?
《名利場》的編輯
The editor of Vanity Fair.
是的  她是我的密友
That's right. She's a close friend.
還有本·格蘭特  波利跳的創始人
And Ben Grant, founder of Pollyhop.
我看到網絡直播了
I saw the webcast.
他們沒有篡改搜索結果
They don't manipulate search results,
但是  如果在《名利場》上大做廣告...
but let's just say a big spread in Vanity Fair...
精彩的選節
Nice juicy excerpt,
托馬斯·耶茨的深度報道  他的文學回歸
profile on Thomas Yates, his literary comeback.
我們本月上了封面  但下個月就可以是你
We're on the cover this month, but... next month it could be you.
我是最民主黨的民主黨
I'm on the Marxist side of Democrat.
我為什么要幫助共和黨
Why would I help a Republican?
你是幫你自己  湯姆
You'd be helping yourself, Tom.
如果順便幫助了我們
And if that helps us a little bit along the way,
又有何不可呢
what's the harm in that?
人人影視傾情奉獻
翻譯  妖精希亞
翻譯  somehacker
翻譯  ET外星人
翻譯  杏仁斯嘉麗
翻譯  煮粥達人
翻譯  國士章魚X
時間軸  Kallen
顧問  老杜
后期  餓得慌
校對  草草
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第四季  第八集
俄亥俄參議員迪恩·奧斯汀
Senator Dean Austen of Ohio,
領導層競選搭檔的首選
the leadership's top choice for running mate.
供職國會12年
Twelve years in Congress,
能幫我們搞定這個重要搖擺州
helps us with a major swing state,
立場中立  極少樹敵
middle of the road, very few enemies,
他們最看重的  是全國步槍協會的老朋友
and most importantly to them, long-time friend of the NRA.
缺點是  也是個中年白人
Now his shortcomings are he's another middle-aged white guy,
平庸無趣
underwhelming, unimaginative
而且是全國步槍協會的老朋友
and a long-time friend of the NRA.
這就是我對領導層這個選擇的態度
So you can see how I feel about the leadership's choice.
參議員
Senator.
我很榮幸  總統先生
I'm honored, Mr. President.
我只有一個很大的顧慮
I just have one major reservation.
-克萊爾  -是的  先生
- Claire. - Yes, sir.
我只跟你說
Well, between you and me,
我都不確定這項槍支法案能否通過
I'm not even sure this gun bill is gonna pass.
但如果要求我支持它
But if I'm being asked to support it,
我很難做...
you know the sort of hot water--
是的  但我需要你作為競選搭檔
Yes, but I need you on the ticket
來平衡我們對待槍支的立場
to balance our stance on guns.
我們還要爭取共和黨的支持
We have to appeal to the Republicans as well.
我不要求你支持法案
And look, I'm not asking you to get behind the bill,
只要不公然反對它就好
just not to publicly trash it.
我知道這對您很重要
I know this is an important issue to you.
確實很重要
It is important,
但不如一名經驗豐富
but not as much as an experienced
能拿下俄亥俄的領導人重要
leader who can deliver Ohio.
那么我同意了  先生
Then consider me on board, sir.
我們不確定能在競選前進入投票
We're not sure we can get this to the floor before the election.
我們有言在先
That's the deal we made.
奧斯汀的事如你們的愿  法案的事如我們的愿
You get Austen, we get the gun bill.
我們首先需要一份強勢的參議院版本
We need a strong Senate version first,
這樣才能避免兩部無力的法案相互調和
so we don't have two weak bills going into reconciliation.
你們想要奧斯汀  就要讓法案通過
You want Austen, you will make this bill a reality.
或者  我們可以重新考慮競選搭檔的人選
Or, we can revisit the choice for running mate.
別  讓我們想想辦法吧
No... let us see what we can do.
我打給米切爾
I'll call Mitchell.
各位
Gentlemen,
有請未來的副總統
the future vice president.
-恭喜  迪恩  -非常感謝
- Congratulations, Dean. - Thank you very much.
-歡迎  -謝謝  安德伍德夫人
- Welcome. - Thank you. Mrs. Underwood.
-認識你很高興  -我也是
- Nice to meet you. - Very nice to meet you.
你們這邊怎么樣了
So, how's it going in here?
我們算是達成共識了  是吧
Well, I think we're in alignment. Wouldn't you say?
這次會面很有成效
It's been a productive meeting.
來談談什么時候宣布吧
So, let's talk about when we should announce.
正式宣布之前  我得安撫一下
I, uh, I need to soften the blow to the NRA
全國步槍協會那邊
before we go public.
一定要保守秘密
It's imperative we keep a lid on this.
絕不能提前泄露
No leaks until we're ready.
只有我們四個知情
Just the four of us in this room.
當然還有克萊爾
And Claire, of course.
我有個簡單采訪要做
Well, I need to go do this quick interview.
米切爾那邊的進展回頭通知我
Um, let me know how it goes with Mitchell.
好了  你肯定有
All right, I'm sure you have some--
開著吧  屋里太憋了
Oh, leave that open. It gets so stuffy in here.
來討論一下時間吧
Let's discuss the timing.
是你還是第一夫人的主意
Was it you or the First Lady?
-完全是第一夫人  -她覺得可以把我爭取過去
- First Lady all the way. - She thinks she can win me over?
她知道你下手肯定最重
She knows you'll hit harder than anyone else.
如果她能堅持到最后  那法案或許就能成
If she's still standing by the end, maybe the bill has sea legs.
-凱特  -早上好  安德伍德夫人
- Kate. - Good morning, Mrs. Underwood.
我們去羅斯福室談吧
How about we talk in the Roosevelt Room?
國會的態度已經搖擺不定了
Support in the House is already wavering.
公眾對槍的興趣也在減退
The public's losing interest in guns.
不等坐下再談嗎
Don't you want to wait until we sit down?
我只有一小時的時間  得充分利用
Your staff only scheduled an hour. I want to make the most of it.
被占了
Oh, it's being used.
換個地方吧
Let's find somewhere else.
凱特
Kate?
縱觀歷史  槍支改革的呼聲潮起潮落
Well, historically, gun reform comes and goes in waves,
你也知道  我認為這次真的會不一樣
as you know, so I believe this time, it can be truly different.
數據全部在這里進行過濾
All the data's filtered here, within these walls.
分析師先初步過濾  最終
My analysts do a first pass, but ultimately,
由我做最后的篩選
I do the final round myself.
我們最關心的是安全問題
Our biggest concern is security.
頂級防火墻  跟國安局總部的一樣
Top-grade firewall, same as you guys use at NSA headquarters.
內部安全呢
What about internal security?
只有我一個有全部權限
I'm the only one with full access.
你要是真發現了什么
So, if you do find anything,
怎么安全地轉達給我們呢
how do you communicate that to us in a secure way?
親自
In person.
我親自去米德堡  或是你過來
I'll come to Fort Meade myself, or you come here.
羞恥
設備不帶出去
No hardware leaves the premises.
能講講你們的過濾算法嗎
Can you walk us through how the filtering algorithms work?
拿槍支為例吧
We'll take firearms, for instance.
從每個合法持有槍支的公民開始
If we start with everyone who legally owns a gun,
通過手機追蹤用戶的地理規律
track geo-location patterns through their phones,
然后描繪一張
we start to put together a portrait
持有者生活  吃飯  購物  等等的地圖
of where gun-owners live, eat, shop, everything.
支持槍控家庭組織
根據這張圖  我們預測未登記
From this, we predict everyone who might want a firearm,
但有意購槍的公民
but who isn't registered.
他們的行為模式很可能與合法持有者類似
They're likely to exhibit the same behavior as people who are.
這可以套用于對阿拉伯語感興趣的人
You can use that for people who are interested in Arabic,
想去中東的人
uh, wanna travel to the Middle East,
或是對美國政府絕望的人
who are disillusioned with the U.S. Government...
跟我們全球監控
So the same techniques that
用的技術差不多
we're using for our international surveillance.
對
Yes...
但先進得多
but far more advanced.
好了  轉過來一點  康威夫人
Okay, turn a little bit towards me, Mrs. Conway.
好
Right.
你真美  漢娜
You look great, Hannah.
-那候選人呢  -別逼我吐槽  威爾
- What about the candidate? - Don't get me started, Will.
-你真上鏡  -我知道
- You're really photogenic. - I know.
弗蘭妮·華萊士  大四那年
Franny Wallace, senior year.
-完全的金魚食譜  -這些是特意擺這兒的嗎
- The all-Goldfish diet. - Did you have these put here specially?
都是最棒的  親愛的
We roll out the platinum carpet, darling.
不知道弗蘭妮現在在干什么
I wonder what Franny's up to now.
反正不是《名利場》的編輯
Hmm, not the Editor of Vanity Fair, I'll tell you that.
或是即將當上第一夫人
Or about to be the First Lady.
我們真是成績斐然啊  不是嗎
Come a long way, haven't we?
是啊  威爾和我  很感謝你這么做...
Yeah, Will and I, um... Will and I appreciate your doing this.
又不是無償的
It's not charity.
這一期有你們倆做封面肯定會賣瘋了
This issue will sell like crazy with you two on the front.
我還是覺得應該報答你
Well, I feel like I should return the favor.
讓我在林肯臥室睡一晚
A night in the Lincoln Bedroom?
一篇報道
A story.
帶副本來了嗎
You have a copy for me?
這是一份摘要
An excerpt.
-我要整本書  -你只能拿到這個
- I need the whole book. - That's all you get.
康威也拿到了一樣的東西
Conway got the same thing.
-這是個錯誤  湯姆  -他們來找我的
- That was a mistake, Tom. - They came to me.
但他們不能發表...除非我允許
But they don't get to publish... without my approval.
你想要什么
So what do you want?
-一次會面  -為了什么
- A meeting. - For?
你只是個傳話人  道格
You're just a messenger, Doug.
你聽到我的話了
You got your message.
給你一周
One week.
謝謝你請的咖啡
Thanks for the coffee.
安德伍德夫人  歡迎
Mrs. Underwood, welcome.
非常感謝您能來錄制這段電話自動語音
Thank you so much for recording this robocall.
這對通過這項法案將有莫大的幫助
It'll go a long way in getting this bill passed.
謝謝你出色的工作
Well, thank you for all the extraordinary work you're doing.
我要去哪里呢
Uh, where would you like me?
薩莉會帶您去我們安排好進行錄音的地方
Uh, Sally will show you where we set up for the recording.
這邊請  安德伍德夫人
Right this way, Mrs. Underwood.
莉安
LeAnn...
那是什么
What is that?
姓名  電話號碼  郵箱地址
Names, phone numbers, emails.
25萬個新目標
A quarter million fresh targets.
25萬  你從哪里拿到的
A quarter million? Where'd you get this?
沒寫回信地址
No return address.
是我們這里掌握的名字的50倍
It's 50 times the names that we have.
是真的嗎
Is it legit?
好像是  我們試著打了幾通電話
Looks like it. We made sample calls.
你好  我是克萊爾·安德伍德
Hello, this is Claire Underwood.
我要坦白一件事...
I need to confess something...
一件我并不引以為豪的事
something I'm not proud to confess.
當我在醫院里坐在我丈夫身旁時
When I was sitting beside my husband in the hospital...
我只考慮到我自己
all I thought about was me.
我的恐懼  一旦我失去他的痛苦
My fear. My pain if I was to lose him.
這是自私的
And it was selfish.
我沒有考慮到其他人
I-- I wasn't thinking about everyone else
那些曾經歷同樣的恐懼和痛苦的人
who had gone through that fear and pain,
那些曾坐在我所坐的位置上
who had to sit where I was sitting
他們所愛的人被不該持有槍支的人射傷的人
because a loved one was shot by someone who shouldn't have a gun.
我感到羞愧  因為我從未對此做過什么
I'm ashamed because I've never done anything about it.
我為本可拯救的那么多生命而羞愧
I'm ashamed of how many lives we could've saved.
那么多家庭本可避免這樣的痛苦
How many families we could've kept from suffering.
我們都應該感到羞愧  我們每一個人
We should all be ashamed, every one of us,
因為我們所有人都有責任
because the blood is on all of our hands,
而什么都不做就等同于扣動扳機
and doing nothing is the same as pulling a trigger.
我們得做點什么
We need to do something.
那就是  修改法律
And that means changing the law.
奧斯汀參議員辦公室
Senator Austen's office.
從下午開始已經接到五百多個電話了
More than 500 since this afternoon.
單單我們區嗎
From our district?
我們都算少的
We have it light.
我聽說其他辦公室接到一千多個電話
I'm hearing that other offices have gotten over a thousand.
奧斯汀參議員辦公室  我會轉達
Senator Austen's office. I will take a message.
弗蘭西斯
Francis.
你真的不該這么做
You really shouldn't.
抽一根不會死的
Oh, one won't kill me.
你讀完了嗎
Did you finish it?
嗯
Yeah.
有一個地方吸引了我
One part really caught my eye.
"一條裂縫在他們之間蔓延開來
"A chasm opened up between them,
那是一條不到九米寬的走廊
a hallway less than ten yards wide.
但它就像有兩千公里那么長
But it might as well have been a thousand miles.
這是一片布置精致的無人之地
A well-appointed no man's land
絲絨地毯和高懸的天花板隔開了兩間臥房
with a plush carpet and high ceiling between two bedrooms.
臥房里住著兩個世紀的鬼魂
In it were two centuries of ghosts,
之前所有的總統和第一夫人
all the Presidents and First Ladies before them.
還有他們婚姻的鬼魂
But also the ghost... of their marriage.
30年的斗爭  讓他們的心都死了
A thirty years' war that left them both dead inside
兩人之間也是一片荒原"
and this dead space between them."
真有洞察力
He's perceptive.
簡直可怕
Uncanny.
那已經不是我們了  已經變了
Well, it's not who we are. Not anymore.
就算是假的  人民還是愿意相信是真的
People will want to believe it's true even if it's false.
你覺得他想得到什么
What do you think it is he wants to accomplish?
我叫你辭職之后  有一晚他來過
He came here one night, after I'd asked you to resign.
他說他很著迷
He said he was obsessed.
也許他還想接著寫
Or maybe he wants back in.
你對他有感情
You felt something for him.
有那么一刻吧
Maybe for a moment.
-你呢  -沒有
- Did you? - No, I don't think so.
我感覺
I felt...
我感覺他看得到我
I felt like he saw me.
我也是
Me, too.
巴恩斯先生
Mr. Barnes.
你打過電話之后  我就一直在想
I couldn't stop thinking, since you called...
佐伊的事
about Zoe.
-我想要個答案  -我也是
- I guess I want answers. - That-- That's what I want, too.
-你想知道什么  -他們有過戀情嗎
- What is it you want to know? - Was there... a relationship?
她和安德伍德
With Underwood?
她17歲時  去上學之前
When she was 17, just before she went off to school...
她發現我有外遇
she found out I was having an affair.
藥物公司的銷售代表
Sales rep, some drug company.
是個金發妞
Blonde. You know.
這是非正式的談話吧
This isn't, you know, on the record.
當然  你不想公開就不公開
No... No, not if you don't want it to be.
你說她發現了
You said she found out.
她給我三天時間向她媽媽坦白  不然就
She gave me three days to tell her mother, or she would...
抱歉  喝了點酒
I'm sorry, I had a few drinks.
-你告訴她了嗎  -告訴了
- Did you tell her? - Yeah, I told her.
我們離婚了
We split up.
那之后佐伊就不怎么理我了
Zoe didn't talk to me much after that.
我不清楚安德伍德的事
I don't know anything about Underwood.
她肯定不會告訴我
I'm the last person she would've told.
我真希望我當初  能多盡點力
I wish I would've... made more of an effort...
跟她溝通
to reach out to her.
你在開車嗎  巴恩斯先生
Are you driving, Mr. Barnes?
對
Yeah.
-我快到家了  -你該停車
- I'm almost home. - You should pull over.
你查到什么了嗎
Did you find out anything?
可以告訴我的事
Anything you can tell me?
她在《先驅報》沒幾個朋友
She didn't have a lot of friends at the Herald.
就我的了解
Um, from what I can gather,
她就沒有親密的朋友
she didn't have any close friends at all.
我跟她鄰里的人談過
I spoke to some people in her neighborhood...
但還沒什么發現
but nothing so far.
你會告訴我嗎
Will you?
-如果查到  -當然
- If you... - Yeah, of course, of course.
如果你想起了什么
If you think of anything...
當然
Yeah.
槍支  陰謀和白宮
那你當時去那兒干什么
Then what were you doing there?
我去白宮開會
If I do a meeting at the White House,
還需要理由嗎  茱莉亞
I don't have to explain myself, Julia.
法案可能會通過
This bill might pass.
-我知道  -你在幫他們嗎
- I realize that. - Are you helping them?
當然沒有
Absolutely not.
-茱莉亞  -安德伍德夫人
- Julia. - Mrs. Underwood.
抱歉  我該跟你握手  但我剛跑步回來
Sorry, I'd shake your hand, but I just got back from a run.
我想說
Listen, I wanted to say,
我知道上次的會面不太順利
I know our meeting last time didn't go very well,
那是怪我  我的話太無禮了
and that's on me. It was rude, what I said,
希望你接受我的道歉
and I hope you'll accept my apology.
請坐吧
Have a seat, please.
你以前進過宅邸嗎
You ever been in the residence before?
套近乎我也不會支持你的
The personal touch isn't going to bring me on board.
給國會打幾千個電話也沒用
Neither will a few thousand calls to Congress.
不到24小時  8.4萬個
84,000 in less than 24 hours.
先不談那個
But let's put that aside for a moment
-來說說你的好朋友  -誰
- and talk about your good friend. - Who?
-奧斯汀參議員  -他說了  競選搭檔
- Senator Austen. - He told me. Running mate.
不只是競選搭檔
Oh, not just running mate.
你說我不必支持這個法案的
You said I wouldn't have to support this bill.
是啊  但是計劃趕不上變化  迪恩
Yes, but a lot can change in a day, Dean.
我們沒想到會有這么大的呼聲
We had no idea there'd be this sort of groundswell.
就因為跟你共處一室
Julia Melman was all over
茱莉亞·梅爾曼就對我逼問個不停
my ass even for being in the same room as you.
你告訴她了嗎
Did you tell her?
-沒辦法  -天哪  迪恩
- I had to. - Christ, Dean...
不然就要樹個死敵
It was that, or make an enemy for life.
她很生氣  但應該能想明白
She's upset, but I think she'll come around,
除非你逼我支持
unless you make me endorse
堵上槍展和網絡賣槍的漏洞
closing the gun show and Internet loopholes.
那她可就要爆發了
Then she'll go ballistic.
迪恩不會的  我們為他的競選出資上百萬
Dean wouldn't do that. We've poured millions into his campaigns.
現在他不需要你了
And now he doesn't need you anymore.
你是要威脅我嗎  逼我們讓步
Are you trying to intimidate me? To get us to back down?
不  我有個提議
No, I have an offer.
民主黨想拿下俄亥俄不容易
Ohio's a tough state for Democrats.
茱莉亞一直對我很好
Julia's been very good to me.
我懂  忠誠是很重要
Loyalty's important, I understand,
但你現在必須忠于我
but your loyalty has to be with me now.
我做不到
I just can't do it.
好吧  那就不公布了
All right, then we'll cancel the announcement.
我另找個競選搭檔好了
I'll find someone else to be my running mate.
不  我沒法支持這項法案
No, I mean, I... I just can't support this bill.
但是現在  兩件事綁在一起了
Oh, but you see, the two go hand in hand now.
你答應不答應
So, are you on the ticket or not?
如果眾議院通過  參議院不通過呢
What if the gun bill passes in the House, but not the Senate?
你要什么回報
In return for what?
你說服參議員退出
You convince the senator to pull out.
領導層想要他  我們也配合了他們
Now, the leadership wants him, and we've played nice,
但我和總統想要的是凱茜·杜蘭特
but the president and I want Cathy Durant.
她參選要更有希望
She's a much stronger candidate.
你愿放棄自己的法案嗎
You're willing to abandon your own bill?
要在擊敗康威和擊敗你之間選
If it's means beating Conway or beating you,
多容易選啊
that's not a hard choice.
我已經告訴迪恩
I already told Dean that
他做競選搭檔我可以接受
I could live with him being running mate.
我怎么能反悔
How do I backtrack?
明天看新聞吧
Just watch the news tomorrow.
你做了正確的選擇
You made the right choice.
-但愿吧  -別但愿  就是
- I hope so. - Well, don't hope so, know so.
我會讓賽斯給你發份講稿
And I'll have Seth send you a copy of the speech.
可以送參議員出去了  謝謝
You can show the senator out now, thank you.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
-抱歉  -沒關系  進來吧
- Oh, I'm sorry. - It's okay. Come in.
-他怎么說  -愿意配合  她呢
- What did he say? - He'll do it. What did she say?
會考慮一下
That she'll think about it.
怎么知道她不會把計劃說出去
How do we know she won't tell him our plans?
我說如果她說出去
I told her if she does,
我們就盡力讓參議院通過法案
we'll make sure the bill goes through the Senate.
給我遞條毛巾好嗎
Can you hand me a towel, please?
-密查姆的手  -什么
- Meechum's hand. - What?
我前一陣在樓下一面墻上畫了個輪廓
I traced it on a wall downstairs... A while back.
被粉刷蓋上了  算了
They've painted over it. Oh, never mind.
弗蘭西斯  我在想耶茨
Francis, I've been thinking about Yates.
康威夫婦什么都有
The Conways have everything.
有孩子  視頻  推特
They have their children, their videos, their Twitter.
沒幾個人理解我們
There are very few people who understand us.
密查姆就是一個
Meechum... was one.
湯姆也是
Tom is another.
八
Eight...
七  很好
Seven. Nice.
長褲子先生
Mr. Long Pants.
好鞋子先生  滾吧  滾吧
Mr. Nice Shoes. Go! Go, go, go.
-滾  -你餓嗎
- Go! - Are you hungry?
不要錢  你走  帶著你的錢走
No money. You need to go. You and your money, go.
-我要叫警察了  -好了  好了
- I'm calling the cops. - All right, all right.
-馬上叫警察  -好了  好了
- The cops, right now... - All right, all right.
-我要叫警察  -好了  好了
- I'm calling the cops. - All right, all right.
女士
Ma'am...
我是湯姆警員
I'm Officer Tom.
是您打的電話嗎
You called for me?
剛剛有個人
There was a man here.
很壞的人
A very bad man.
-您住在這街區嗎  -33年了
- Do you live on this block? - Thirty-three years.
3  3
Three... three.
在這兒見過這個壞人嗎
Did you ever see this bad man on your block?
好吧
All right.
那這個女人呢  見過她嗎
What about this woman? Did you ever see her?
-真美  -是的  是很美
- Pretty. - Yes, yes, she is.
婊子
Whore!
-滾開  -為什么那么說
- Go away! - Why'd you say that?
-滾開  滾開  -為什么那么說  告訴我
- Go away. Go away. - Why'd you say that? Tell me.
告訴湯姆警員  為什么那么說她
Tell Officer Tom. Why did you call her that word?
滾開
Go away!
我和兒子親手建的
Built this myself, with my son.
他明年春天要爬船長峰
He's doing El Capitan next spring.
徒手攀登
Free-climb.
我覺得競選總統
I feel like running for president
就像不系安全繩爬懸崖
is like climbing a cliff without a safety rope.
對了  媒體怎么不知道你在這兒
How is it the press don't know you're here, by the way?
像你一樣  將軍
Just like you, General,
我周末也會休假  陪陪家人朋友
I take Sundays off to spend time with family and friends.
或是交新朋友
Or to make new friends.
州長  我知道你還是希望我辭職
Look, Governor, I know you still want me to resign.
但我之前不該拿那個做威脅
But I was wrong to threaten that.
德雷爾告訴我哈里發國這周又占領了一塊油田
Dreyer told me ICO took over another oil field this week.
他們的勢力在壯大
They're growing.
德雷爾什么都跟你說啊
Dreyer shares a lot with you, doesn't he?
這就發生在你眼皮底下  將軍
This is happening on your watch, General.
總統不作為  你也不能逼他
The president isn't acting and you can't force him to.
只要你留下就不能
Not if you stay.
不過你要是辭職  我保證你還會有工作的
If you resign, though, I promise it'll only be temporary.
我一扯上政治  就回不了頭了
Once I get political, I can't cross back over the line.
我不是要等上任后重新委任你
I don't mean a recommission.
我要讓你做我的競選搭檔
I mean making you my running mate.
謝謝
Thank you.
-讀了嗎  -只讀了摘要  很有力
- Have you read it? - Just an excerpt. It's powerful.
會很有爭議  答應我我就給你看
And it'll be controversial. Say yes and I'll show you.
《電訊報》不會允許的
The Telegraph would never let me.
-母公司都是我們家  -那也不行
- Same parent company, both our titles. - Doesn't matter.
報社對打兼職有很明確的態度
Paper is strict when it comes to moonlighting.
沒關系  因為我爸爸是董事
It does matter, because my dad is on the board.
給你的編輯打個電話
One call to your editor...
會有很多人搶著要這個機會
There... there are plenty of people who would jump at doing this.
但沒有對他那么"了解"的人
Not who know him intimately.
我的新競選記者
My new election correspondent,
看到你和耶茨在競選途中溜出去了
he saw you and Yates sneaking off on the campaign trail.
耶茨會對你坦言的
Yates will open up to you.
你肯定知道該怎么出招
I'm sure you know what buttons to push.
有利益沖突
It's a conflict of interest.
我爸爸給我看了你寫的文章
My dad showed me that article you wrote.
你叫他暴君  沒發表出來的那篇
The one that never went to print where you called him a tyrant.
有些人的職業是靠聲譽打下來的
Some of us have built our careers on our reputations,
而不是靠擺弄爸爸給的雜志
not by having their daddies give them a magazine to play with.
或是跟老同學套近乎
Or by cozying up to old school chums, right?
這些話我都聽過
I've heard it all before.
你可能不喜歡我  不喜歡康威夫婦
You may not like me, you may not like the Conways,
但我覺得比起讓安德伍德再干四年
but I have to believe you can stomach us better
你會更愿意接受我們
than another four years of President Underwood.
-寫得不錯  -我知道
- Well, the writing is good. - I know.
但還不足以脅迫總統
Not good enough to strong-arm a president.
倒是能讓我進到這屋里來
Well, good enough to get me in this room.
我以為弗蘭西斯跟你說清楚了
I thought Francis made it very clear to you,
你不能挑釁我們
you were not to challenge us.
是啊  他說他會告訴全世界
Yeah. He said he would tell the world
《天蝎》不是我寫的
I didn't write Scorpio.
我希望你明白
I hope you understand
我們不能允許你在選舉前出版這本書
that we can't allow you to print this before the election.
我明白
I do.
那你為什么想見我
Then why did you want to meet?
我需要個結尾
I need an ending.
我有個還湊合的結尾  但我不喜歡
I have one I can live with, but not the one I love.
-因為是假的  -你的確走了
- Because it's false. - Well, it's true that you left.
我要是走了  就不會在這兒了
If I left, I wouldn't be here.
我根本不相信
I don't believe for a second
你去拜訪你母親是因為她病了
you went to visit your mother because she was sick.
為什么
And why is that?
因為你一次都沒跟我提過她
Because you never mentioned her one time to me.
有時候只字不提能代表千言萬語
Saying nothing says a lot sometimes.
要是故事重點不是她如何離開
Well, what if the story isn't about how she left,
而是她如何回來呢
but how she came back.
你在這里  不代表你全身心都在
Just because you're here doesn't mean you're here.
你肯定想知道吧
Well, wouldn't you like to know?
你不是想要結尾嗎
Don't you want your ending?
你要跟我說嗎
Are you gonna tell me about it?
關于你們倆  不許說謊
About the two of you? No lies.
不  我什么也不說
No, I'm not going to tell you anything.
你可以像以前一樣觀察
You can observe, like you did before.
不過這次  你所見到的一切都屬于你
The difference is everything you see this time will be yours.
我們想得到點東西作為回報
And in return, we would like something.
講稿  我們需要了解我們
Speeches. We need someone who knows us...
也了解我們態度的人
and knows our voices.
講稿撰稿人  你開玩笑吧
A speechwriter? You're kidding.
只有這個辦法能解釋你為什么和我們在一起
It's the only way to justify you being with us...
以防媒體問起
in case the press ask.
你們是想盯著我
You want to keep an eye on me.
我覺得挺公平的  不是嗎
Well, I think that's fair. Don't you?
如果你要盯著我們的話
If you're keeping an eye on us?
你給我們一周  我們就給你一天
So you gave us a week. We'll give you a day.
就是在這里  在這個地方
It was right here, on this very spot,
我被一支非法獲得的手槍
that I was shot with two bullets
所射出的兩顆子彈擊中
from an illegally obtained handgun.
特勤局特工艾德華·密查姆
Secret Service Agent Edward Meechum,
前海軍陸戰隊隊員  也是我的朋友
a marine and my friend,
因同一支手槍射出的子彈而犧牲
was slain with the bullets from that very same gun.
最近幾天
The public support...
公眾對第一夫人的《背景普查法案》的
for the First Lady's... Universal Background Check Bill
支持呼聲震耳欲聾
has been deafening in these last few days.
我們聽到了成千上萬人的呼聲
We have heard from thousands and thousands of voices,
今天  我們想向其中再增加一個聲音
and today, we would like to add one more voice to that chorus.
這聲音強而有力
And it is a powerful voice.
俄亥俄州迪恩·奧斯汀參議員
Senator Dean Austen of Ohio.
謝謝您  總統先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
我十多歲起就是全國步槍協會的成員
I've been a member of the NRA since I was a teenager.
我一直都是持槍權利的強烈支持者
I've always been a fierce advocate for gun rights.
但今天我要強力支持
But today I want to offer my strong support
第一夫人的法案
for the First Lady's bill.
給你
Here you go.
-我再問你一個問題  -我告訴你  伙計
- Let me ask you another question. - I'm tellin' you, man,
你要是說她住在這個街區  我相信你
if you say she lived on the block, I believe you.
但她肯定不喜歡披薩
But she must not have liked pizza,
因為我不記得見過她的臉
'cause I don't remember ever seein' her face.
不是她  安德伍德總統
Not her. President Underwood.
天啊  這人真是陰魂不散
Oh, Christ, I can't get away from this guy.
他妻子剛剛給我打了電話  關于槍的自動電話
His wife just called me. Robocall about guns.
你在這附近見過他嗎
You ever seen him around this neighborhood?
見過  經常見到
Oh, yeah. All the time.
周五晚打過保齡球后和英國女王一起
With the Queen of England, Friday nights, after bowling.
在他還在國會的時候
When he was in Congress.
一次都沒見過
Nah, never once.
否則我會記得的  我擅長記面孔
I would've remembered. I'm good with faces.
-帕爾瑪干酪  -在那邊
- Parmesan? - Over there.
但這個人我見過幾次
I saw this guy a few times, though.
-參議員  -不  那個死掉的人
- The senator? - No, the, uh, the dead guy.
那個特勤局的
The Secret Service guy.
在這兒嗎
In here?
是啊  他之前經常來喝咖啡
Yeah, a while back. He used to stop in for coffee.
不吃披薩  只喝咖啡
Never any pizza, just coffee.
-你確定嗎  -我說過  我擅長記面孔
- You're positive? - Yeah. I told you, I'm good with faces.
"起落架收起了  幾秒鐘之后
"The wheels lifted, and within seconds,
華盛頓就消失在
Washington fell away, disappearing
一團煙霧中了
under a blanket of haze and smog.
她前額頂著窗戶
Forehead pressed to the window,
想象一千年前
she imagined this was exactly
這里肯定也是這番景象
how it must have looked a thousand years ago,
太陽升過云端
when the sun rose above the clouds
而下面只有一片沼澤
and there was nothing but a swamp beneath.
在這個高度  看到這番景象
From this height, with this view,
她可能是在任何地方
she could be anywhere.
但關鍵是  她不在那里"
But the important thing is she was anywhere but there."
終
-還要一杯嗎  -要
- You want another? - Yeah.
終
他說為什么了嗎
Did he say why?
謝了  戴娜
Okay, thanks, Dana.
耶茨退出了
Yates pulled out.
說他跟安德伍德夫婦達成了協議
Said he came to an agreement with the Underwoods.
他拿我們相互做籌碼
He was playing us off each other.
我們還是可以放出摘要
We could still leak the excerpt.
太冒險  不被人查到還好
It's too risky. If we get away with it, great.
要是被查到
If we don't,
我們就成了坑害知名小說家的投機分子
we look like opportunists fucking over an acclaimed novelist.
不值得
It's not worth it.
你覺得他們之間真的有裂痕嗎
Do you think it's true, that chasm between them?
誰知道
Who knows?
我喜歡他的文筆
I love that writing.
-真希望能看到剩下的  -我討厭《天蝎》
- I wish I could've read the rest of it. - I hated Scorpio.
-寫得多美  -就是垃圾
- It was beautiful. - It's garbage.
-為什么  -主角是個慫貨
- Why? - The main character's a pussy.
-威爾  你知道我討厭那個詞  -他就是
- Will, you know I hate that word. - He is.
他最好的朋友自殺  他卻袖手旁觀嗎
He lets his best friend kill himself. He does nothing?
他很痛苦  反正也要死了
He was in pain. He was going to die anyway.
那也不重要  還是懦弱
It doesn't matter. It's cowardly.
我覺得他很勇敢  他朋友也是
I think he was brave. And his friend.
我覺得耶茨能寫出來也很勇敢
And I think Yates was brave to write it.
勇敢是不放棄  無論如何戰斗到底
Brave is never giving up. You fight, no matter what.
如果耶茨同意了  凱特·鮑德溫本來也會同意
So, Kate Baldwin was willing if Yates was in?
是啊  戴娜讓她寫兩萬詞
Yeah, Dana was giving her 20,000 words.
應該可以再斡旋一下
I think we can pivot.
怎么做
How?
再給她打個電話
Get her back on the phone.
-茱莉亞  -奧利維亞  都不知道你來了
- Julia. - Olivia, I didn't know you were in town.
就是來看看
Oh, just a little visit.
我有時候還挺想迪恩的  別告訴他
I miss seeing Dean's face sometimes. Don't tell him that.
-能讓我們單獨談嗎  -她不用走
- Will you give us a few minutes? - No, she should stay.
我知道你們有事要談
Oh, I know you have things to discuss.
比如你丈夫放棄做競選搭檔
Like your husband withdrawing from the ticket.
她是為此而來吧  跟你一起宣布
That's why she's in town, right? For the announcement.
我知道那個新聞發布會肯定讓你很意外
I know the press conference must've caught you off guard,
但總統不想讓你知道
but the president didn't want you to know.
-他覺得你會組織抗議  -他說對了
- He thought you'd organize a protest. - He was right. I would've.
我希望能坐下  宣布之前好好談談
My plan was to sit down, talk this out before the announcement.
沒什么好宣布的了
There isn't gonna be an announcement.
你不能大搖大擺走進來
You... you can't waltz in here--
你丈夫初出茅廬時
We've raised $20 million
我們就給他捐了兩千萬
for your husband since he was a freshman.
我就可以隨時大搖大擺走進來
That gives me the right to waltz in whenever I want.
-放尊重點  -親愛的  行了
- Show some respect. - Honey, please.
不  這是我們要的
No. This is what we wanted.
-我們奮斗的目標  -等安德伍德輸了
- What we've worked for. - When Underwood loses,
你接下來兩年可就有仗要打了
you'll spend the next two years fighting off a primary opponent.
我們在俄亥俄的二十萬會員都會反對你
Every one of our 200,000 members in Ohio will turn on you.
等你沒了這個職位
By the time you've lost this office,
奧利維亞的律所也會黃了
Olivia's law firm will go tits up.
別忘了  我們給你引了好多客戶
Don't forget, we pushed most of your clients your way.
他臨陣退縮了  我能怎么辦
He got cold feet. What can I do?
勸他改主意
Convince him to change his mind.
他不聽  他說全國步槍協會對他嚴詞威脅
He wouldn't listen. He says the NRA came down hard on him.
因為你讓他做了新聞發布會
Because you had him do the press conference.
不  那是奧斯汀的主意  不是我的
No, that was Austen's idea, not mine.
我跟他說了要低調
I told him to lay low,
但他說如果他要加入  就要完全投入
but he said if he was in, he wanted to be all in.
我們的打算是平衡你們兩人的立場
The idea was to balance the ticket.
奧斯汀這條路已經不通了
Well, we can't do anything about Austen.
問題是我們能找誰來代替他
The question now is who do we get to replace him?
再看看名單
Go back to the list?
他還好  但那張名單上別人我都沒興趣
He was fine, but I'm not enthused by anyone else on that list.
別又回到起點了  總統先生
Let's not go back to square one, Mr. President.
我們有張不錯的名單
We have a good list.
大家都會支持那些人的
Everybody can get behind those names.
這是常理
It's common sense.
常理唯一的問題就是  太普通了
The only problem with common sense is that it's so... common.
我覺得我們有更好的選擇
I think we can do better.
誰
Who?
凱茜·杜蘭特
Cathy Durant.
路易斯安那不是搖擺州  這我清楚
Now, Louisiana's not a swing state, I know that.
但她仍然是個全國知名人物
But she is still a national figure,
她能幫助我們爭取女性選民的選票
she helps us with the women's vote,
并且我信任她
and I trust her.
槍支呢
What about guns?
她似乎對此立場并不堅決
I don't think she's ever had a strong position.
比那更好  她對這個問題從未發表過意見
It's better than that. She's never uttered a word on the issue.
我們查過了
We checked.
-我喜歡  -我也是
- I like it. - So do I.
-但我還有個想法  -誰
- But I had another thought. - Who?
不是"誰"  是怎樣
Not "Who." How.
我覺得不應該由我選她
I don't think I should choose her.
我認為應該由黨選她
I think the party should choose her.
你不是說開放黨代會吧
Not an open convention.
鮑勃  我們
Look, Bob, let's...
我們必須面對事實
We have to face the fact that
我的健康狀況將會對我們非常不利
my health is gonna be a major liability for us.
不論誰做競選搭檔
No matter who becomes the running mate,
那人最終都可能成為總統
they could well end up being president.
那種情況
Now, that is a...
我甚至都不愿想
a scenario that I don't even like to fathom,
但是我們無法回避
but we can't escape it.
如果這個決定如此重要
And if it's such an important decision,
為什么不讓黨做定奪呢
why not let the party make it?
因為那樣大家都可以參選
Because it'd be a free-for-all.
不不  我們要想辦法讓凱茜獲勝
No, no. We make it so that Cathy wins.
只是要做得像是黨選擇了她
We'll just make it look like the party chose her.
想想新聞報道吧  會鋪天蓋地的
And think of the coverage. We'll own the news.
你想把黨代會變成馬戲表演
You want the convention to be a circus.
鮑勃  我不知道你有沒有注意到
Oh, Bob, I'm not sure if you've noticed or not,
但政治已經不只是戲劇了  是娛樂業
but politics is no longer just theater, it's show business.
那我們就演一出最棒的戲吧
So let's put on the best show in town.
太好了
Great.
能向我敬個禮嗎  將軍
Will you give me a salute, General?
現役軍人不能接受媒體采訪
Active military aren't allowed to speak to the press.
他今天早上辭職了
He delivered his resignation this morning.
不是吧
No shit.
只等總統同意  我們立刻就在網上發布
We're gonna break it online as soon as the president accepts it.
月刊不常得到這種首發猛料吧
Not often a monthly gets raw meat like this, huh?
他的電話會被打爆的
His phone's gonna blow up.
但你會得到獨家采訪
But you get the exclusive.
-湯姆的事很遺憾  -我不覺得
- Sorry about Tom. - I'm not.
謝謝你  將軍
Thank you, General.
好了  我們要準備...
All right, we're gonna go set up for the...
下午好  將軍  我是凱特·鮑德溫
Good afternoon, General. Kate Baldwin.
我們開始吧
Shall we?
不用說  安德伍德夫人
So, the main issue that Mrs. Underwood
最近關注的主要問題是槍支
has been focusing on is guns, obviously.
我們準備了一些最近在用的談話要點
We've got some talking points we've been using,
-你想  -抱歉  有水嗎
- so you'll want to... - I'm sorry, is there any water?
有
Yes.
我有點宿醉
I'm a bit hungover.
至少現在清醒了
At least I'm not still drunk.
要來點嗎
Want some?
不用
Uh, we're fine.
好
Right.
那么
So...
談話要點
to the talking points.
什么事
What is it?
幾位容我失陪一下
Excuse me for a moment, gentlemen.
我最想說的  是死亡人數
What I want to communicate mostly is about the death toll,
個人經歷  以及那些能打動...
with personal stories, things that connect with--
克萊爾
Claire.
-湯姆  -總統先生
- Tom. - Mr. President.
能談談嗎
Can we speak?
那么  你們兩個繼續
I'll, uh... I'll leave you to it.
她真的在乎什么槍支問題嗎
Does she actually give a shit about guns?
她在不在乎有什么關系
What's that got to do with anything?
我們知道會有這種可能
We knew this was a possibility.
他會鬧出很大動靜  肯定是康威搞的鬼
He's gonna make a lot of noise. It's Conway, I'm sure of it.
問題不在康威  而是莉安
Problem isn't Conway, it's LeAnn.
是她強力主張取消空襲的
She pressured us to cancel the air strike.
已經做出的決定  就不要多想了  道格
We chose our path, Doug. Let's not second-guess it.
請原諒  安德伍德夫人  但是她有害
No offense, Mrs. Underwood, but she's doing damage.
我認為應該踢掉她
I think we should replace her.
我們要通過槍支法案就得靠她
She's the reason we're gonna pass the gun bill.
先生  《名利場》主編戴娜·崔斯特
Sir? I just got this from Dana Treister,
剛給我發來了這個
the editor of Vanity Fair.
我不確定是什么意思
Not sure what it means...
他打算把這老混蛋定為競選搭檔
He's gonna make that son of a bitch his running mate.
-什么情況  -我去查查這個人
- What's goin' on? - I'll see what I can dig up on him.
不  他當初擔任
No. He was fully vetted
參聯會主席時已經徹底審查過了
when he was commissioned for the Joint Chiefs.
你和賽斯就他的辭職起草一份聲明
No, you go with Seth and draft a statement on the resignation.
好  先生
Yes, sir.
-走  -什么情況  道格
- Let's go. - What's going on, Doug?
都怨莉安
And it's LeAnn's fault.
要不是她  他根本不會辭職
He never would've resigned if it wasn't for her.
你去查查
See what you can find.
將軍嗎  總統說不用查了
On the general? The president said we shouldn't.
去查莉安
On LeAnn.
我可不想攙和辦公室政治
Hey, I don't wanna get involved in some cage match--
我們不是說過了  你得服從我
I thought we had an understanding. Your obedience.
我盡量去查
I'll see what I can do.
你同意道格嗎  你對莉安有疑慮嗎
Do you agree with Doug? You're having reservations about LeAnn?
對湯姆的疑慮比對她要大
Less about her and more about Tom.
不過我說了相信你的判斷  我就會相信你
But I told you I trust you on this, so I'm trusting you.
-領導層同意了嗎  -他們有疑慮
- Has the leadership agreed yet? - They're skeptical.
我們可以利用這個
We can use this.
先生們  如果你們對
Well, gentlemen, if there was
黨代會還有什么疑慮的話  放下吧
any doubt about an open convention, let it go,
因為我們必須把這則新聞蓋下去
because we're gonna wanna bury this news.
布洛哈特剛剛辭職了
Brockhart has just resigned.
將軍馬上就要登上《名利場》的封面了
And the general is about to appear on the cover of Vanity Fair.
想想康威會怎樣大加利用吧
Imagine what Conway can do with that.
康威  康威  康威
Conway! Conway! Conway!
多謝你們到來
Thank you for coming.
謝謝
Thank you!
多謝你來支持我
Thank you for coming out.
-戴娜給我發了這個  -很高興見到你
- Dana just sent me this. - So great to see you.
消息發布了
The story broke.
-你好  -我妻子多完美啊
- Hello. - Isn't my wife perfect?
謝謝
Thank you.
讓她聽聽你們多喜歡她
Let her know how perfect you think she is!
別鬧
Stop it.
你真討厭
You're too much!
-謝謝  謝謝  -康威  康威  康威
- Thank you! Thank you! - Conway! Conway! Conway!
2013年
11月
我知道  福斯托
Yeah, I know, Fausto.
我也是光想想都覺著累
I get exhausted just thinking about it, too.
2013年9月
2013年
10月
11月
2013年
12月
好了
All right.
萬里長征第一步
A journey of a thousand miles.
艾德華·密查姆  出行記錄
13年5月1日-13年6月30日
■
1996年出版的小說《風起云涌》(Primary Color)
講述了一個來自美國南方州的州長競選總統的故事
故事中的州長有一位非常強勢的夫人
還好拈花惹草  與身邊其他女性有染
小說于1996年1月出版后引起巨大轟動
占據《紐約時報》暢銷書排行榜榜首九周之久
讀者很快發現小說是在影射時任總統克林頓和夫人
情節也是以克林頓參加1992年大選時的事件為藍本
該書出版時作者為"無名氏"  一些人經過文本分析后
認定作者為《時代周刊》專欄作家喬·克萊恩
但克萊恩最初斷然否認  直到四年后才公開承認
該書曾于1998年被改編搬上大銀幕